Finding aid for the Robert A. Kennard Papers LSC.2351
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 4: Increasing diversity in architecture, 1976-1994
  - AIA Workshops re: Black/White Joint Ventures, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Howard University - Listing of African American AIA Fellows, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - National Organization of Minority Architects - Various Notes, 1974-1984 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Summer Intensive Orientation Program - Cal Poly Pomona, 1984-1987 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - National Organization of Minority Architects - Membership, Constitution, Bylaws, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - AIA Draft Reports, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - List of African American Architects, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Los Angeles National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Membership, 1975-1985 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - African American Architects in Current Practice, Princeton Architectural Press, 1992 (Box 62)
- Accession LSC-2351-2017-08 backlog material, LSC-2351-2017-08